(Penny:)I guess that joke's only funny
in Nebraska.
(Sheldon:)From the data at hand,
you can't draw that conclusion.
(Sheldon:)All you can say with absolute certainty
is that that joke is not funny here.
(Penny:)Boy, it's good to be back.
- How's your family?
- Oh, it was the worst trip.
(Penny:)- Everyone got sick over the weekend.
- Sick?
(Leonard:)Here we go.
- What kind of sick?
- Oh, the flu, I guess.
(Sheldon:)I don't need you to guess,
I need you to know.
(Sheldon:)Now, when did the symptoms
first appear?
(Penny:)Maybe Friday.
(Sheldon:)Friday. Was that morning or afternoon?
(Penny:)- I don't...
- Think, woman.
(Sheldon:)Who blew their nose and when?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, relax.
She doesn't have any symptoms.
(Leonard:)I'm sure she's not contagious.
(Sheldon:)Oh, please.
(Sheldon:)If influenza was only contagious
after symptoms appear...
...it would've died out years ago.
(Sheldon:)Somewhere between tool using
and cave painting...
...Homo habilis would've figured out
to kill the guy with the runny nose.
(Leonard:)Penny, you'll have to excuse Sheldon.
He's a bit of a germaphobe.
That's okay. I understand.
(Sheldon:)Thanks for your consideration.
Now please leave.
(Leonard:)You'd better go
before he starts spraying you with Lysol.
(Penny:)Okay, well,
thank you for getting my mail.
(Leonard:)No, problem. Welcome home.
[CAN SPRAYING]
SHELDON:
What?